(Howard:)I have an idea.
(Howard:)What if we put a post
on Craigslist that says:
"World-class Caltech physicist
seeking girlfriend.
"If interested,
(Howard:)solve the following puzzles
for a chance to meet him."
(Sheldon:)Oh, we'll make the puzzles
extremely challenging
(Sheldon:)to eliminate
unworthy candidates.
(Raj:)Oh, we could set it up
like a scavenger hunt where
(Raj:)the last puzzle gives the winner
Sheldon's contact information.
(Howard:)Well, this is actually an
interesting social experiment.
(Raj:)I'm a little jealous of the
people who get to do it.
(Howard:)Me, too.
(Howard:)And we've seen the prize.
(Leonard:)I don't understand why we're
leaving so early for the movie.
(Penny:)Oh, I forgot to tell you...
we're gonna meet up
(Penny:)with Bernadette to spy
on Amy and her date.
(Sheldon:)What?
(Leonard:)I don't want to do that.
(Penny:)What, and you think I
want to see a documentary
about aluminum can
recycling?
(Leonard:)This is the movie
(Leonard:)Big Soda doesn't
want you to see.
(Penny:)No, it's the movie your wife
doesn't want you to see.
(Leonard:)So you're actually okay
(Leonard:)with invading
your friend's privacy?
(Penny:)You're not curious
who she's out with?